tvguide.co.uk 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy - TV Guide UK TV Listings

|  TVGuide.co.uk Privacy Policy  

This Policy identifies our current privacy policy with respect to any information you enter on our site www.tvguide.co.uk, mobile apps, and Apple TV and any information derived whilst you are visiting these. This policy applies to every visitor to our site.

**Do you gather information about my browsing patterns on the site?**

 ****

We do gather information about your browsing patterns and activities throughout this site, however this information cannot be used to identify you and neither can we derive any personal information from this. It is gathered purely to enable us to track site statistics and to administer any difficulties relating to our site. This information is not made available to any third party.

**What additional information do you store on TVGuide.co.uk apps and Apple TV and how will this be used?**

We store all interactions a user has with the app, including alerts, programme clicks, programme and channel favourites, calendar additions and watch lists. The information we store cannot be used to identify you and nor can we derive any personal information from this. We only use this information to track app statistics and will not make this information available to any third party.

**When I provide you with any personal information, what will it be used for? **

Any personal information provided through to us by you, will be stored so that we can provide you with a more personalised service. We will only use this data to identify you. We will not pass your data on to any third party or company. We may from time to time send you information regarding our products and services, which you have shown an interest in.

**Will you send or sell any personal information I pass on to you on to a third party? **

We do not now and have no intention in the future to sell on or rent any information you pass to us to a third party. If we do use third party services we require and we ensure to our best ability that any information they hold is handled with the strictest confidence.

**How safe is the information you hold about me? **

We are committed to keeping your information as secure as is physically possible by us. We also use additional methods to secure sensitive information about your activities with us. Every employee that works for TVGuide has to follow a strict confidentiality procedure and privacy standard.

**How safe are the third party web sites you link to? **

From time to time we may hyperlink to other Web sites on the Internet, if TVGuide does not run these sites, we are not responsible for the content they hold on their site and the privacy procedures they run on their sites. However if we find a company is abusing the information they are passed we will remove that link from our site.

**Do I need to register to use your site? **

You do not need to register to use the public part of this site.

When you visit our website, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a website to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

Advertisements on our site are provided by another organisation. Our advertising partner will serve ads that it believes are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to this and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number). In order to do this, our advertising partner may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. For more information about this type of online behavioral advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this features off, please visit <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/>

If you have any further question regarding our policy please contact us using our feedback page
